// creating an array and passing the number, questions, choices, and answers
const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many strings does bass guitar have?",
    choices: ["4", "5", "8", "6"],
    answer: "4",
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the name of the second string of a standard guitar?",
    choices: ["G", "B", "A", "C"],
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Plectrum is another name for which guitar accessory?",
    choices: [
      "Guitar Head",
      "Guitar Pick",
      "Guitar Strings",
      "Electric Pick-ups",
    ],
    answer: "Guitar Pick",
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The guitar is a part of which string instrument family?",
    choices: ["Membranophone", "Electrophones", "Idiophones", "Chordophone"],
    answer: "Chordophone",
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many strings does a guitar usually have?",
    choices: ["4", "7", "6", "5"],
    answer: "6",
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When were electric guitars introduced?",
    choices: ["1930s", "1950s", "1960s", "1920s"],
    answer: "1930s",
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many types of acoustic guitar exist?",
    choices: ["5", "4", "6", "7"],
    answer: "7",
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the name of the fourth string of a standard guitar?",
    choices: ["B", "D", "A", "C"],
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which guitarist did not play with slides?",
    choices: ["Elmore James", "Robert Johnson", "B B King", "Brian May"],
    answer: "B B King",
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many frets are there on a standard classical guitar?",
    choices: ["19", "20", "21", "22"],
    answer: "19",
  },
];
